我叫Oliver Queen
My name is Oliver Queen.
被困在孤岛上5年以来
我只有一个目标...活下去
For 5 years,I was stranded on an
island with only one goal... survive.
Oliver Queen还活着
Oliver Queen is alive.
现在 我要完成我父亲的夙愿
Now I will fulfill my
father's dying wish...
根据他留给我的名单
除掉那些毒害我城市的人
to use the list of names he left me and
bring down those who are poisoning my city.
为了完成目标 我必须扮成别人
To do this,I must become someone else.
我必须掩盖身份
I must become something else.
绿箭侠 前情提要
Previously on "Arrow"...
谁给你的致幻剂
Who supplies you with Vertigo?
他们叫他伯爵
They call him the Count!
56个人死于研发这种快感
56 people died to perfect this high.
警方从未抓到杀了你哥的人
The police never caught
your brother's shooter.
子弹上有箭毒
这是Floyd Lawton的手法
The bullets were laced with
curare,that's Floyd Lawton's M.O.
- Lawton还活着
- 我很抱歉 John
- Lawton's alive.
- I'm sorry,John.
这个叫Lawton的人踢了他的狗吗
This Lawton guy kick
his dog or something?
他杀了他的哥哥
He killed his brother.
我们怎么样
How we doing?
有盈余 也有亏损
We're in the black,and the green.
我喜欢把钱扔进俱乐部再收回来
I like how we've gone from throwing
money at clubs to catching it.
看看这些
Oh,look at these.
什么生意会做到失物招领处
都是女人的内衣啊
What sort of business has a lost and found
that's just filled with women's underwear?
最好的生意吗
The best business ever?
这么欢乐肯定犯法了
Ohh,having this much fun
should be against the law.
噢 希望是这样
Oh,if wishing made it so.
抱歉 打扰你们了吗
Sorry,am I interrupting anything?
- Laurel还好吗
- 她很好
- Is Laurel ok?
- She's fine.
我来是为了别的事
This visit is about something else.
有个女孩在附近街区出车祸了
A girl just got mowed down
a couple blocks from here.
在斯特林大桥
On Starling bridge.
你们俩有印象吗
Ring any bells with you two?
- 没有
- 真的吗
- No.
- Should she?
她今晚来过你们俱乐部
She was in your club tonight.
很多人都来过
A lot of people were.
你觉得有人杀了她
You think someone killed her?
不是某人
Not someone.
是某样东西
Something.
致幻剂
Vertigo.
是的 你们俱乐部有这个吗
Yeah. You got a problem
with that in this club?
我不知道
Not that I'm aware of.
这里我们不允许带毒品 警官
We don't allow drugs in here,Detective.
控制好你们的客户群
Control your clientele.
以防又有人跑到马路上乱晃
Before anyone else wanders into traffic.
她有可能带毒品进来吗
Is there any chance she could
have scored the drugs in here?
我怀疑 我尽量没雇太多毒贩子
I doubt it. I try not to
hire too many drug dealers.
给我一份员工名单
Get me a list of employees,anyway.
我让Felicity去查他们的毒品拘留记录
I'll have Felicity cross
reference it for drug arrests.
也包括咱俩了
That includes the two of us,you know.
我以为义务警员已经解决伯爵的案子了
I thought the Vigilante
finished off the Count.
我是解决了
I did.
医生 我就问他几个问题
I just need to ask him
a few questions,Doc.
你可以试试 警官
但我不确定你能问出什么来
Well,you're welcome to try,Detective,but
I'm not sure you'll get very far with him.
什么意思
What does that mean?
是因为医生病人保密协议吗
Is this a load about
doctor-patient privilege?
不 他服用过量的未提炼致幻剂
No,far from it. The unrefined
Vertigo overdose he suffered
导致他的前扣带皮层末梢有所损伤
caused damage to the caudal
portion of his anterior cingulate.
好吧 你可能会因为
我没上过医学院而惊讶
Well,you'll probably be shocked to
hear that I didn't go to medical school.
我和他已经处了几个月了
I've been working with
him for months now.
他只会说些分裂性言语
还会偶尔对你吐痰
And all I've gotten out of him is word
salad and the occasional spit in the face.
- 祝你好运
- 谢谢
- Best of luck to you.
- Thanks.
我生于此地 死于彼地
Here I was born,and there I died.
有一刻是因为你
It was only a moment for you.
你不曾发觉
You took no notice.
今晚一个女人死于你的毒品
A woman died tonight...
from your poison.
很多女人会在很多夜晚死于不同的原因
Lots of women die,lots of
nights,for lots of reasons.
又有人在出售致幻剂了
都是从哪里来的
Someone is selling Vertigo
again. Where is it coming from?
我记得你
I remember you.
帽衫侠
Man in hood.
你一直在我的脑海里
You are never far from my thoughts.
你让这座城市失望了
You have failed this city!
你可以直接说他是个疯子
You could have just said he was nuts.
你让这座城市失望了
You failed this city!
好了 我学到了一招
All right! You're teaching me that one.
还差不知道刀的位置
Only if you show me where the knife was.
谁教你打架的
Who taught you how to fight?
我爸希望生的是儿子
My father wanted a son.
这不就是吗
He got one.
当心点 这支弓能承受150磅的重量
The tension of that bow's 150 pounds.
一失手你俩眼睛里就都是纤维碎片了
Snap it,you'll both be covered
by fiber shrapnel in your eyes.
她说的没错 你不够强 孩子
She's right. You're
not strong enough,kid.
再来吗
Go again?
真不错啊 你俩都很强悍
It's pretty exciting that
both of you are such bad asses,
你们也许可以计划下怎么阻止Fyers
but do you think that maybe we
should be making a plan to stop Fyers?
还有...救你父亲
And,I don't know... Save your dad?
他一直这么怨念吗
Does he always whine this much?
今天算不错了
Today's one of his good days.
他会打架吗
Can he fight?
我试着教过 但从未成功
I've tried. Never much success.
我坐等呢
I'm sitting right here.
我还没试过
Well,I haven't tried yet.
Patterson议员被狙击手射杀
a***
- John叔叔
- 嘿 小盆友
- Uncle John.
- Hey,buddy.
你能读"Logan Bogan"的故事给我听吗
Will you read "Logan Bogan" to me?
宝贝 上床去 等会妈妈念给你听
Sweetheart,get into bed and mommy
will read to you in a minute.
我要John叔叔给我念嘛
But I want Uncle John to read to me!
John叔叔今天很累了
Uncle John's had a long day.
下次再念给你听
He'll read to you next time.
抱歉
Hey,I'm sorry.
我今天一直在外面
I've been some place else today.
你怎么了
What's going on with you?
我在查一些事情
I'm just trying to
figure some stuff out.
需要谈心的话 我一直在
If you need to talk about
anything,you know I'm here for you.
是Oliver Queen 有急事
It is Oliver Queen,with an emergency.
我得走了
Got to go.
我尽快赶来了
Got here as quickly as I could.
是你爸小册子上图案的事吗
This about the glyph in
your father's notebook?
Felicity还在查
Felicity is still working on that.
有别的事了
We have another problem.
斯特林市又陷入了
人尽皆知的致幻剂之战
Starling City is once again at war with
the drug known on the streets as Vertigo.
它曾是这里最致命的东西
It used to be the
city's most lethal vice,
但这绿紫色药丸已经消失三个月了
but the purple and green pill was
nowhere to be found for the last 3 months.
过去几天 我市因为
新型的致幻剂血流成河
Over the past few days,the city has been
flooded with a new version of Vertigo.
它更易上瘾 更不稳定
More addictive,more unstable.
导致俱乐部的一个女孩死了
It killed a girl in the club.
就像当初差点要了Thea的命
Just like it almost killed Thea.
那你怎么想 去见见伯爵吗
Ok,what are you think? We
should pay the Count a visit?
已经见过了 白去
He was my first visit. Waste of time.
他已经疯了
He's...sumasshedshiy.
但他是唯一一个知道致幻剂配方的人
Since he was the only one that
knew the forumla for Vertigo,
我不知道从何下手了
I don't... I don't even
know where to begin.
很好 你们都在
当然都在 你们还能去哪
Good,you're here. Of course you're
here. Where else would you be?
你们可爱死这里了
You clearly love it down here.
来看看这个
You got to see this.
我现在在警方几小时前公布的
一个精神病患者逃离的现场
I'm here at the scene where police say a
disturbed patient escaped only hours ago.
当局立即宣布封锁斯特林市
精卫中心以追查此次越狱事件
Authorities issued an immediate for Mental Health
lockdown at the Starling County Institute following the breakout.
警方提醒市民不要接触叫伯爵的毒贩
Police are warning people to avoid contact
with the drug dealer known as the Count.
一点也不疯狂吧
Not so crazy after all,huh?
-=伊甸园美剧 http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-
-=伊甸园字幕站 http://ytet.org=-
荣誉出品
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-
-=http://ytet.org=-
Proudly Presents
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=-
翻译: 看糖 Ducky 旖旎
校对: AndreaQuinn
时间轴:3p
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-
-=http://ytet.org=-
Sync:3p
绿箭侠
第一季 第十九集
720p版本调校：C.Ronaldo
Arrow
Season 1 Episode 19
720p版本调校：C.Ronaldo
我在给他吃药 他在喃喃自语
I was administering his
meds. He was babbling.
他惯例吼闹 然后突然不说话
His usual ranting,then he's ice cold.
一下子压制住我
He overpowered me.
他逼我从维修出口带他出去
He forced me to take him out
through the maintenance exit.
我以为他无害 正如你所说
I thought he was harmless.
Basically a vegetable,you said.
我知道 这几个月我一直在观察他
I know. Which means... I've interviewed
him dozens of times in the past few months.
- 这么被一个病人完全欺骗...
- 别担心 我们会找到他的
- To be deceived by a patient so completely...
- Don't worry. We'll find him.
会让他进一个无法逃离的监狱
He's going to find prison a
lot harder to break out of.
警官 他很危险
Detective... He's dangerous.
千万别低估他
Don't underestimate him.
监控录像里能找到什么吗
Did we get anything from
the security cameras?
根据这里的规定
Not according to the orderly here.
为了节省预算 第一个拆的就是摄像头
Due to budget cuts,the
cameras were the first to go.
真是荒唐
That is unbelievable.
还有别的途径
There's another angle.
Veronica Sparks
那个从俱乐部出来的受害者
Veronica Sparks,the
dead girl from Verdant?
我查了她的用户数据信息
I checked her LUDs.
她死前最后联系的人是Tommy Merlyn
The last person she texted
before she died was Tommy Merlyn.
他说不认识她
He said he didn't know her.
Merlyn被指控两项罪名
其中一项是蓄意谋杀
Merlyn has two collars for
possession,one with intent.
对 那是5年前的事
Yeah,that was over five years ago.
或许他更擅于逃脱法网
Maybe he's just better at
not getting himself arrested.
Laurel说他爸不给他钱以后
他改变了很多
Well,Laurel says he's changed
ever since his father cut him off.
人总是秉性难移
Yeah,a leopard and his spots,you know?
或许在他的夜店贩毒
只是维持他以前生活作风的一种方式
Maybe pushing Vertigo at his new club is
a way of maintaining his old lifestyle.
是啊 或许去找Meryln
Yeah,or maybe going after Meryln's
a great way to get my daughter
能让我女儿别再跟我闹僵 Hilt
to stop speaking to me again,Hilt.
Quentin 我了解你的难处
Look,Quentin,you know I get that.
还有 凭直觉 我查了夜店的账户
But here's the thing... on a hunch,I
subpoenaed the club's bank accounts.
他们的营业费用中有1万美元亏空
There's ten large missing
from their operating expenses.
你觉得Merlyn用那些钱买致幻剂了吗
You think Merlyn spent
that money on Vertigo?
我很纳闷 那么多钱花哪儿了
I think I can't explain how that
much money just gets misplaced.
我会继续查的
Look,I'll take a run at it.
- 你别管了
- 不
- Keep you out of it.
- No.
还是我来吧
I should do it.
需要什么
What you need?
好嘞
All right.
黑哥哥我弄来了你要的毒品
The person of color has
successfully purchased your drugs.
别忘了 我说过我去的
For the record,I offered.
追踪器激活时 我们怎么知道呢
How will we know when
the tracker is active?
已经激活了 我们在钱上植入的纤维
已经在发信号了
It already is. I'm getting a good signal off
the monofilament strips we placed in the bills.
贩毒的钱就像鸽子 总能找到回家的路
Drug money's like a pigeon...
it always finds its way home.
追踪那些钱 我们就能找到伯爵
We can follow the money all
the way back to the Count.
继续追踪
Ok. Keep tracking it.
这些致幻剂 你要怎么处理
Well,what are you going to do
with all the Vertigo you bought?
办个派对呗 Felicity
Plan on having a party,Felicity?
我仅有的涉毒经历是大一那年
My only experience with
drugs was an encounter
无意中吃了含大麻的巧克力蛋糕
with a pot brownie my
freshman year... by mistake.
本来应该挺嗨的 可是我对坚果过敏
Which could have been
fun,except I'm allergic to nuts.
头部中枪
All right,head shot.
又有人被杀 是个议员
Kills again,this time a U.S. senator.
在哪儿追踪到他的
Where have you been tracking him?
不远处 我用他Floyd Lawton那个化名
查了我能想到的所有法律类数据库
Not very far. I ran his Floyd Lawton alias
through every conceivable law enforcement database.
他给一个Alberto Garcia的人
打过几次电话
He's made a series of
calls to an Alberto Garcia.
根据国家安全局的记载
Garcia是个不错的黑社会伯乐
According to NSA,Garcia's a
reputed underworld talent scout.
他帮Deadshot接的活儿
He books all the Deadshot's hits.
- 没查到更多 但...
- 查到这些已经不错了 Felicity 谢谢
- It's not much to go on,but...
- Yeah,but it's something,Felicity,thanks.
你觉得该告诉Oliver吗
Don't you think Oliver should know?
不用 这是我的私事
No,this is personal.
我自己处理Lawton的事
Lawton is my problem to deal with.
什么风把你吹来了
What brings you by?
嘿 一起吃晚饭吧
Hey,would you like some dinner?
你女儿点了超多泰国外卖
Your daughter ordered
way too much Thai food.
不用了 谢谢
No,thanks.
我是来谈公事的
This is a business visit,actually.
关于Sparks那个女孩的命案
我想问你几个问题
I got some follow up questions
on the Sparks' girl's death.
好啊 那女孩出车祸前去过我的夜店
Sure. The girl was in the
club before she got run-over.
你说不认识她 但她手机里
最后一条短信是发给你的
You said you didn't know her,but,um,but
the last text off her phone was to you.
是吗 那...我可倒霉了
Really? Because,uh...
Well,I'll be damned.
我没回复
Huh. Well,I didn't reply.
这种垃圾短信 我每晚收到无数条
I get a hundred texts like this a night.
大家想去夜店玩
People wanting to get into the club.
那女孩说"要勾搭我吗"
只为了进夜店吗
So that's what she meant
by,"Can you hook me up?"
要不还能为什么
What else would it be about?
你们夜店的账户少了1万美元
$10,000 is missing from
your club's bank accounts.
钱去哪儿了
What'd you spend the money on?
不知道 可能是记错账了
No idea. There must be some
sort of bookkeeping error...
我打开天窗说亮话吧
Ok,let me put this another way...
如果你为了"勾搭"你的顾客
用那笔钱去买致幻剂...
if you spent that money on Vertigo so
that you could "hook up" your clientele...
爸
Dad!
现在你最好配合警方 这事你别管
Then the best thing for you right now is
to cop to it,ok? Get out in front of this.
什么也别说
Don't say anything.
- 我是想...
- 公事公办吗 我知道了
- I am trying to...
- To do your job? Yeah,I know.
我也一样
And this is me doing mine.
Laurel 我知道我现在
又成了不招人待见的老爸
Laurel,I know I look like the
disapproving father...again.
但我不来 别的警察就会来
But I came down here
so another cop wouldn't.
明白吗
You understand?
- Tommy 我...
- 我没胃口了
- Tommy,I...
- I'm not hungry anymore.
手举起来
Hold up hand up.
掌心对着我
Palm facing me.
击打水面
Hit the water.
- 什么
- 快点
- What?
- Hit it.
再来
Again.
再来 用力
Again. Harder.
想让我看起来像个二B吗 你做到了
If the point of this is to make
me feel like an idiot,it's working.
"不积跬步无以至千里"
"A journey of a thousand miles
begins with a single step."
孔夫子名言 很好
Confucius,great.
跟你爸一样
I'm starting to see
the family resemblance.
是老子的名言 再来
Laozi,actually. Again.
到底要干嘛
Now what?
盛满水 再来
Fill the bowl. Start again.
有线索没
What have you got?
查到了钱最终的去向
The end of the money trail.
我把交易地点发给你
Sending the dealer's
location to you now.
谁想嗨一嗨
Who's looking to party?
这可不够 哥们
That's not enough,man.
付不起钱就别想嗨
You don't pay,you don't play.
没关系 薄利多销
It's all right. Good for business.
我老板好像挺喜欢你 G
My boss seems to like you,G.
这个 够买一大包了 老兄
Now that... That'll
buy you a brick,my man.
快跑
Go,go,go!
保持呼吸
Don't forget to breathe.
他不会的 我不会的
He won't. I won't.
恭喜
Congratulations.
我正式封你为超级大怪咖
You're officially the
creepiest person I've ever met.
我 我感觉不好
I don't...I don't feel so good.
别靠近我 怪咖
Get away from me,creep.
怎么回事
Have we got a problem?
你没事吧
Are you ok?
各部门请注意 发生袭警事件 呼叫救护车
All units,all units,code 99.
有持枪者在斯特林水族馆 各部门...
417 in progress,Starling
Aquarium. All available units...
警方频道刚播的
this just came over
the police frequency.
我黑进了水族馆的安保系统
能看得更清楚
I hacked the aquarium security
system to get a better look.
想难为我吗你
You want
围观者看见他吃过黑色和绿色的药
Bystanders said they saw him
pop some green and black pills...
有个服用致幻剂 嗨过头的家伙
劫持了人质
There's a lunatic high on
Vertigo who's taking hostages,
你却在...泡茶
and you're making... making tea.
那是我从岛上带来的草药
They're medicinal herbs from the island.
有解毒功效
They counter balance the effects
of certain drugs and poisons.
应该可以解致幻剂的毒
They should counteract
the effects of Vertigo.
- 你不想...
- 什么
- And you aren't going to...
- What?
你懂的...
You know...
我妹妹服食过那破玩意儿
My sister got high on this garbage.
差点闹出人命
Could have killed someone.
但她罪不至死
She didn't deserve
an arrow in the heart.
那家伙也没危害本市
This guy didn't fail the city.
是本市害了他
The city failed him.
我也害了他
And so did I.
这不是你的错
What's happening now isn't your fault.
你又没逼他吸毒
You didn't make him take drugs.
是 可我没干掉伯爵
No,but I did fail to put
the Count in a grave so deep
要不他也不能再害人
that he couldn't come
back and hurt anyone again.
你抓到他了 他也被关起来了
You caught him. They locked him up.
现在本市在水深火热中
And now the city is on fire!
很显然 只把他抓起来是不够的
So clearly,it wasn't the right decision.
联系Diggle
Get in touch with Diggle.
监控系统受损
我需要有人在水族馆帮我望风
With the security feed out,I'm going
need a second set of eyes at the aquarium.
你回国时能见上面 真高兴
Glad I caught you stateside.
可不 两天后我要去平壤
Just barely. I leave in
two days for Pyongyang.
这不是秘密吗
Isn't that classified?
老战友肯定会为我保密的
I figure an old army
buy can keep a secret.
很高兴接到你的电话
I was glad to get your call.
Lyla 我打给你不是为了叙旧
Lyla,that's not why I called.
那你是要我帮你忙咯
There's something else you'd
like me to do for you,then.
实际上 是我要帮你
Well,actually,I think there's
something I can do for you.
我快陷入孤立无援之地了
我想Deadshot是Argus的头号通缉犯
I'm going to go out on a limb and assume
that Deadshot is on Argus' most wanted list.
你掌握了些什么
What do you know about him?
第一 他叫Floyd Lawton
Well,his name,for
starters. Floyd Lawton.
我们都没查到呢 你怎么知道的
We don't even have
that. Where'd you get it?
我还有这东西
Same place I got this.
这里面的信息
能查出Deadshot的幕后指使
This is everything you need to locate
who's giving Deadshot his targets.
你为什么对这事上心
What's your interest in this?
Lawton跟我在从事的一些事有关
Lawton came up in connection
with some things I'm working on.
我觉得这些信息给你最合适
I thought you were the right
person to pass it off to.
你以前说谎可没这么差劲 Johnny
I remember you being a
better liar than that,Johnny.
Lyla  Lawton是危险分子
Listen,Lyla,Lawton is
a very dangerous man.
你们才有能力把他绳之以法
And your people are the most
qualified to take him down.
就这么简单
It's that simple.
我们的工作从不简单
Nothing in our business is simple.
又需要我帮什么吗 Lance先生
Me to ask for my help again,Mr. Lance?
Eric Messner吗
Eric Messner?
谁
Who?
斯特林市城区规划委员
He's a zoning commissioner
for Starling City.
而且是出了名的腐败
A notoriously corrupt one,at that.
那失踪的一万元
就是你贿赂他免于检查你们俱乐部
Missing ten grand. You paid it to him
to skip the inspection of your nightclub.
为什么这么做 Merlyn
有什么你不想让他发现的
Why'd you do that,Merlyn? What
didn't you want him to find?
没有啊
We got nothing to hide here.
好 那我四处转转
Great. Then let's just
take a little look around.
没问题
Absolutely.
但必须有搜查令
When you come back
with a search warrant.
你确定要这么来
Are you sure this is how
you want to play this?
当然
Apparently.
我女儿还真会挑人
Doesn't my daughter
know how to pick 'em.
不许笑我
Stop laughing at me!
闭嘴
Shut up!
别吵
站住 我不想伤害你
Stop! I don't want to hurt you.
我是来帮你的
I'm here to help you.
我妈会瑜伽
My mom does yoga.
还记得Slade和我救你的时候吗
Hey,remember when
Slade and I rescued you?
你救的我
You rescued me?
行 我们互救的时候
Fine. When we all rescued each other.
你说你知道Fyers为什么
要抓姚飞逼他帮忙
You said you knew why Fyers wanted Yao
Fei,and how he was forcing him to help.
想说说吗
Feel like sharing?
我们没可以拍的水了
We're almost out of slapping water.
我父亲是人民解放军的将军
My father was a Shangjiang in
the People's Liberation Army.
上将 我不知道Fyers计划的细节
A general. I didn't hear
the details of Fyers plans,
但他想让我爸去应对
but he wants my father
to be the face of it.
做替罪羊 承担过失 隐藏内幕
A scapegoat. To take the blame
and conceal their own involvement.
姚飞一开始怎么会来这的
Why was Yao Fei on the
island in the first place?
Fyers说他杀了人
Fyers says he murdered people.
没有
No,he didn't.
中国军方承认了大屠杀
The Chinese military
comitted the massacre.
得有人承担过失
Someone had to take the blame.
他们就选择了他
They chose him.
把他遣送到这座岛度过余生
Sent him to this island for life.
我找他找了很多年
I spent years looking for him.
几个月前 有人找上了门
A few months ago,a man
came to my apartment.
说他知道我父亲的下落
Said he had information
about my father's whereabouts.
我当时已经不抱希望了
I had given up hope.
就放下警戒 没看到他带了电击枪
直到在这里醒来
Let my guard down. Didn't see the tazer
until... When I woke up,I was here.
我很担心 在这座岛上只为了生存
I'm worried. This island... What
he must have had to do to survive.
这会不会改变他
That it changed him.
他救过我的命
He saved my life.
他还是好人 Shado
He's still a good man,Shado.
再来吧
Again.
我就这么坐在我们最爱的寿司店
So there I am sitting at our
favorite Sushi restaurant,
喝着清酒 只缺佳人
a bottle of saki,and the only thing
that's missing is my boyfriend.
天哪 我真的很抱歉 亲爱的
My God,I'm so sorry,baby.
这里事情太多了
I just have a lot going on here.
Tommy 不管发生什么事
你要知道我都相信你
Tommy,whatever's going on with
you,I want you to know I believe you.
我都站在你这边
I'm here for you.
不好意思
Sorry.
Ollie
Ollie.
怎么了
What's wrong?
今晚糟透了
Bad night.
事情变糟了 Meryln先生
根据你的要求 搜查令已到
It's about to get worse. Mr. Meryln,as
requested,a warrant to search these premises.
- 我不敢相信你这么做
- 相信吧
- I can't believe you're doing this.
- Believe it.
警官 我不是律师
Detective,I'm not an attorney,
但你为什么要搜我的俱乐部
but on what grounds are
you searching my club?
你的总经理贿赂了一个政府官员
Your general manager
bribed a government official
让你们的楼免于检查
to keep him from inspecting
the entirety of your building.
什么
What?
因为他在店里出售致幻剂
Because he's selling
Vertigo out of the club.
- Ollie 这是有效的
- 谢谢
- Ollie,it's valid.
- Thank you.
地下层不在检查楼层内
A sub level is not listed on
the inspection's floor plans.
但我查了县里记录
However,I pulled the county records.
下面有东西
There's something down there.
我想亲眼看看是什么
I want to see for myself what it is.
在那
Oh,look at that.
开门吧
Open the door.
你这是在犯错
You're making a mistake.
不 是你
No. You are.
如果你不开门的话
If you don't open that door.
我说开门
I said,open the door.
谢谢
Thank you.
这地方真是一片乱
The place is kind of a mess.
我用它来储藏我们大部分存货
I've been using it to store
the bulk of our inventory.
箱子里是什么
What's in the boxes?
你自己看啊
Why don't you have a look.
如果禁酒令还有效的话
Well,if prohibition
were still in effect,
你有刑事诉讼依据了
you might actually have a
basis of a criminal complaint.
想打开其他板条箱吗
Would you like to open
the rest of the crates?
既然你们没什么需要藏的
So if you don't have anything to hide...
为什么这里不让检查
Why didn't you want
the inspector down here?
这里的通风系统六十年代之后就没换过
Well,the ventilation system in this place
hasn't been updated since the sixties.
也许我们都没法营业
Maybe we shouldn't even be open.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我以为他能接受我们在一起
I thought he was ok
with us being together.
他没错 我是贿赂了那个人
He wasn't wrong. I bribed a guy.
那他也不该使这种高压手段
That's not why he
brought out his jackboots.
会没事的
It's all gonna be fine.
回家见
I'll see you at home.
- 晚安
- Good night.
有什么想跟我说的吗
Is there something
you want to say to me?
谢谢你
Thank you.
我不明白你为什么不告诉我贿赂的事
No,I meant the thing when Lance accused me of
that you were thinking dealing out of the club.
我经营着俱乐部 Oliver
I don't understand why you wouldn't I run the club,Oliver.
just tell me about the bribe.
很多事我都没告诉你
I don't tell you a lot of things.
我倒要问问你了 兄弟
So let me ask you a question,pal.
你回来的这半年我做了什么
What have I done in the last
6 months since you've been home
会让你相信我贩毒了
that would lead you to believe
that I would sell drugs?
过去半年吗 没有
In the last 6 months? Nothing.
但我失踪之前 你行为卑劣
Before I left,you played hard.
你总是跟那些坏人在一起
You played with bad people
who were into bad stuff.
你又何尝不是 Oliver
And so did you,Oliver.
但我和你一样变了
But I changed just like you did.
现在你拿箭指着那些违法的人
Now you put arrows in
people who do illegal things.
贿赂检查员是违法的
Last time I checked,bribing a
city inspector was not legal.
你真的以为我会伤害你吗
Do you actually think
that I could hurt you?
其实我完全不知道你会做出什么来
Truthfully,I have no idea
what the hell you would do.
你对我来说像迷一样
You are a complete mystery to me.
我不知道你如何做到轻易地去杀一个人
I've got no idea how you find
it so easy to kill people.
下次你认为我有多恶劣时
想想我是怎么认为你的
The next time you decide to think the
worst of me,imagine what I now think of you.
他怎么了
What's his problem?
你怎么了
What's yours?
什么意思
Excuse me?
我让Felicity联系你
I asked Felicity to
get in touch with you.
水族馆有人劫持人质
There was a hostage
situation at the aquarium.
抱歉 之后我才看到消息
I'm sorry,I didn't get that
message till it was over.
怎么会
Why?
我在处理别的事
Because I was busy doing something else.
Lawton
Lawton.
Oliver 你最后并不需要我
Oliver,you didn't end up needing me.
你怎么会知道呢
You couldn't have known that.
你不是自己去找杀你哥哥的凶手了吗
In other words,find your brother's
killer on your own time,right?
致幻剂在腐蚀这座城市 Diggle
Vertigo's tearing
this city apart,Diggle.
没错 也许现在是解决
私人恩怨的最佳时机
So,yeah,maybe now's not the best
time to indulge a personal vendetta.
你现在敢跟我说
你去找伯爵不是擅自去的
You're actually gonna that you going after the
stand there and tell me Count is not personal?
Oliver 听着 在不知道是Lawton
夺走了我侄子的父亲前
Oliver,listen,I cannot
read a book to my nephew
我没法给他讲故事
without knowing that Lawton
took his father from him.
我没法和Carly在一起
I can't move on with
Carly,I can't move on
知道他还活着我没法前进
with my life knowing
that he's still out there.
我以为只有你会懂我
I thought if anybody
got that it'd be you.
这里怎么了
What happened here?
这里的网还能用
The ethernet cable still works.
接上你的电脑吧
Would you plug in your tablet,please?
你想重建吗
Did you decide to remodel?
说来话长
Long story.
Dig呢
Where's Dig?
一言难尽
Long story.
那个劫持人质者是瘾君子
The hostage-taking junkie.
他现在是我们能找到伯爵的唯一线索了
He is the only lead to
the Count we've got left.
你要什么信息
What type of information
are you looking for?
只要能让我知道伯爵的位置就行
Anything that will give us a
line on the Count's location.
验尸有结果了吗
Has the M.E. performed
the autopsy report yet?
马上调出来
Yeah,just pulling it up now.
查一下毒物学
看是否有和他用的致幻剂相关的东西
Check the toxicology to see if there's
something related to the Vertigo he was on.
他不是使用致幻剂过量死的
He didn't die of a Vertigo overdose.
我看到了 Felicity
I saw it,Felicity.
验尸官说是死于严重的过敏反应
According to the coroner,cause
of death was severe anaphylaxis.
他是因氯丙嗪过敏而死的
He died of an allergic
reaction to chlorpromazine.
那是抗精神病药
That's an anti-psychotic.
看一下Veronica Sparks的尸检
Pull up the Veronica Sparks autopsy.
她体内有氯丙嗪吗
Did she have chlorpromazine
in her system?
有
Yes.
你怎么知道
How did you know?
伯爵肯定已经把它加进
最新一批致幻剂了
The Count must have added it as a new
ingredient in this latest iteration of Vertigo.
但他生产这些
不需要庞大的社交圈来推销吗
But wouldn't the amount he'd need to
manufacture enough for circulation be huge?
这从何而来
Where would he get that much?
精神病院
A mental institution.
万一我们都想错了怎么办
What if we're looking at this all wrong?
怎么会
How so?
每个人都在救济院之外的地方找他
万一他从没离开过呢
Everybody is looking for him outside
the asylum,but what if he never left?
万一他假装自己跑了
就像他装疯一样
What if... What if he faked his escape
the same way that he faked being insane?
我本该抓住机会杀了你的
I should have killed you
when I had the chance.
转过去
Turn around.
我让你转过去
I said turn around.
Oliver Queen
Oliver Queen.
在岛上的那么多年 看来你真是疯了
All those years on that island.
所以伯爵不是装疯 对吧
So the Count didn't fake
losing his mind,did he?
一直都是你
This was you the whole time.
你怎么让他把致幻剂的配方给你的
How'd you get him to give you
the formula for Vertigo? Huh?
现在化学不像是他的强项了
Chemistry doesn't seem like
his best subject right now.
他要不想说是不会告诉我的
He couldn't tell me if he wanted to.
我给他的肾脏做了个活检
I ordered a biopsy on his kidneys.
在他吸毒过量后 纸巾上全是麻醉药
The tissue was suffused with
the narcotic after his O.D.
拿到结果以后
我意识到我可以逆向推出
When I got the results,I
realized I could reverse engineer
药物的化学成分
the chemical compound of the drug,
用这里的设备 制造一种合成版本
produce a synthesized version
myself using the facilities here.
也有一些改进 比如加入氯丙嗪
And made a few improvements,like
adding chlorpromazine.
你就是这么找到我们的
That's how you found us.
有警察来询问
Cops came around,started
asking questions,
你假造了伯爵的失踪
来减少别人对你的关注
you faked the Count's disappearance
to draw attention away from yourself.
很聪明
It's clever.
我没想过要当犯罪主谋
I wasn't trying to be
a criminal mastermind.
我只想要钱而已
I just needed the money.
你这亿万富翁当然不会懂
Something I'm sure a
billionaire wouldn't understand.
相信我 我懂你
Believe me,I understand you perfectly.
掰开他的嘴
Open his mouth.
什么 不
What? No! No!
我从小报里了解到
From what I've read in the tabloids,
人们听说Oliver Queen吸毒过量而死
是不会惊讶的
no one will be surprised to hear
Oliver Queen died of a drug overdose.
安全
Clear.
不许动
Freeze!
你看起来可不怎么好
You don't look so good.
我觉得你射不准的
I doubt you could aim a single arrow.
看来我是站到最后的那个
Looks like I'm the last one standing.
坐着 旋转
Sitting. Spinning.
做点什么
Something to do.
我本来要做什么
What was I going to do?
记忆和原来的不一样
Memory not what it once was.
什么都变了
Nothing what it once was.
墓碑上有名字吗
Is there a name on the gravestone?
没有
No.
是新的
It's new.
很干净
And clean.
在等着
And waiting.
这里完事了
We're finished here.
怎么样
Hey. How we doing?
不怎么样
In the black.
帽衫侠找到他的人了么
Did the Hood get his man?
我们不会再因为致幻剂惹上麻烦了
Well,we won't be having any
problems with Vertigo anymore.
Tommy 我很抱歉
Look,Tommy,I'm sorry.
我一直在记账
我记的存货的单子都在这
I've caught up the bookkeeping and all
my notes on the inventory are in there,
有我们用的供应商的清单
along with a list of
suppliers that we use.
好
Ok.
我不懂你为什么要跟我说这个
I don't see why you're telling me that.
这个俱乐部对我很重要
This club is important to me.
但对你来说就是个幌子
But for you it's just a front.
你想让我帮你保守秘密
帮你做你的帽衫侠
You want me to keep your secret,help
you be this thing you've become,
但你却看不到我所成为的人
but you refuse to see
me for what I've become.
我把这个看的有点太重了
I've got just a bit too
much self-respect for that.
我不干了
I quit.
吃饭吧
Dinner.
你还在弄呢
You're still doing that?
Fyers最好小心他那碗水
Fyers better be careful
with his bowls of water.
我们什么时候才能实际演习
When are we going to do actual training?
有个男孩被他爸爸放到少林寺
There once was a young boy
whose father dropped him off
去学功夫
at a shaolin monastery to study Kung Fu.
很好 讲上故事了
Good,a story.
一年以后 男孩回家
After a year,the boy
came to visit his family.
问他学到什么了的时候
男孩羞愧的低下头
When they asked what he'd learned,the
boy hung his head in shame.
和尚就让他拍桶里的水整整一年
All the monks had him do was
slap water in a barrel for a year.
我们没有一年时间
We don't have a year.
所以我希望你的训练方案能快一点
So I hope your training
regimen is a bit faster.
家里都不相信他
他就演示给他们看
The family didn't believe
him,so he showed them.
他举起手去拍他们吃饭的桌子
He raised his hand and hit
the table they were eating on.
桌子碎成两半
It broke in half.
我能击碎一个桌子吗
I'm gonna be able to break a table?
比那个还厉害
Better.
好吧
Ok.
拉弓
Draw the bow.
真见鬼
I'll be damned.
然后呢
What's next?
我们教你射箭
We teach you to shoot.
自己喝酒吗
Drinking alone?
没有 不再喝了
Oh. Well,no,not anymore.
就喝苏打水
Just soda?
酒保忘了放酒吗
Bartender forget the scotch?
我觉得我不需要那个了
I didn't really feel the need for it.
那个死了的女孩
她的致幻剂是从一个同事那来的
So,um,the girl who died,it turns out
that she got her Vertigo from a co-worker.
看来我要跟你男朋友道歉了
Guess I owe your boyfriend an apology.
他有名字的
He has a name,you know.
我就是不太习惯叫
Yeah,I just can't seem
to bring myself to use it.
起步阶段
Baby steps.
我又毁了咱们之间的关系吗
Did I screw things up between us again?
没有
No.
听着 我不是有意刁难Merlyn 好吗
Look,I really wasn't
looking to jam up Merlyn,ok?
我知道追查他的话 能让他犯错...
I knew by pursuing him that
I could throw a wrench in...
那你为什么这么做
Then why did you do it?
有证据的 Laurel 我必须遵循那个
There was evidence,Laurel,and
I had to follow it. I had to.
你妈妈是对的 你是对的
Look,your mom was right,you were right.
就像你说过 我和那个义务警员
我放不下的
Like you said about me and the
Vigilante,I can't let things go.
我销案了
I close cases,it's what I do.
其他人可不理解
Everyone else be damned.
也许你不喝酒代表着
你准备好去解决这件事了
Well,maybe the fact that there's no scotch
in there means you're ready to work on that.
人是可以改变的
People can change.
你挺我
You had my back.
你需要我
You needed me.
Felicity告诉我你去哪了
Felicity told me where you were headed.
你还好吗
You ok?
我是杀手 记得吗
I'm the killer,remember?
我杀过人 Oliver
I've killed before,Oliver.
就那么一阵
It's just been a while.
如果你是杀手
为什么伯爵没有死
If you're the killer,why
isn't the Count down,too?
我知道你肯定很想除掉他
I'm sure it must have been tempting
to take him off the board for good.
人是可以改变的
People change.
像伯爵那样的人
People like the Count?
不 我是说我
No. I meant me.
要是不久前 我一定会杀了伯爵的
Not so long ago I would have
put that guy down for good,
但是看着他那样茫然 杀他毫无意义
but looking at him today all vacant...
There didn't seem to be a point.
但不是所有人都值得你的仁慈
But not everybody deserves mercy.
比如
For example.
我以为他不是你优先考虑的
I thought he wasn't a priority to you.
他是你优先考虑的
He's a priority to you.
你有两个未完成之事
You two have unfinished business.
我们从哪开始
Where do we start?
我不想再说"我早跟你说过"
但夜店经营得很不成功
I'd prefer we skip the I-told-you-sos,but
the nightclub wasn't really working out.
我想我需要一些更无聊 更安稳的事
I guess I need something
more boring,stable.
朝九晚五 回家吻Laurel这样的事
9:00 to 5:00,go home kiss
Laurel,that sort of thing.
我想说的是 我想要一份工作
I guess what I'm saying
is... I want a job.
--------------------------
本论坛字幕仅翻译交流学习之用
禁止任何商业用途否则后果自负
--------------------------
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-
-=http://ytet.org=-
Proudly Presents
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=-
翻译: 看糖 Ducky 旖旎
校对: AndreaQuinn
时间轴:3p
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-
-=http://ytet.org=-
Sync:3p
绿箭侠
第一季 第十九集 完
720p版本调校：C.Ronaldo
Arrow
Season 1 Episode 19
720p版本调校：C.Ronaldo